Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Why are we forced to work?!
丿\ンマ一へッ ド
なぜ働力ヽなければいけないの力ヽ ! 一
Why must we pay money in order to eat?!
なぜ金を払わないと
飯が食えないのか一
Can't we all just share?
分け合えばいいじやない力` ! _
The rich get fat while the poor die!
金持ちは肥え 貧乏人は死ぬ ! _
Where is the true freedom in this world?!
こんな世の中の
何力ヾ自由なのだ ! 一
We are all slaves to our work!
皆 労働に
縛られ亡いるではないか一
And is work fun?
仕事は楽しい力`? _
No! How could it be?!
そんなわけない ! _
不ー
ロ・
We do not want to work, period!
我々は断固 働きたない!
That's why I, Hammerhead,
will change our society
だ力ヽら変えるのだ
このハンマ一へツ ド力ヾ!
into one where only those who want to work
will work, while the rest are supported!
働きたい奴だけ働いて
他は養ってもらえる社会に!
理想郷を実現させるのだ !
We will create a utopia!
The Paradisers led by me, Hammerhead,
will make all this a reality!
とうげんだん
このハンマ一へツ ド率いる桃源団力ヾ!
Boss, no one's listening.
ボス! 誰も聞い亡ません‥
What?!
何だと ! 一
Bah! These civilians are idiots!
そ~ 惠力`な大衆どもめ
Let's go!
行ぞ
Zeniru's the richest man in town.
We'll wreck his posh penthouse and show them we're serious!
まずは田〕一番の大富豪
ゼ二一丿しの家を破壊し亡
本気だと分力`らせてやる !
High-rise apartments are symbols of inequality!
ハンマ一へツ ド 豪邸など一
子供 ハゲ
不平等の象徴だ
母親コラ 見ちゃダメ
Yes, sir!
団員たち イ工ツサ一
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
This whole building is Zeniru's home.
この高層ビル
丸ごとゼ二一丿しの自宅で曹
There's no way he made so much money legally.
悪いことをして
荒稼ぎしたに違いない!
Unforgivable! Bring it down!
許せん! 破壊しろ!
Yes, sir!
イ工ツサ一
ドツソ一イ!
Target destroyed!
標的を破壊しました !
Hm, these experimental
battle suits sure pack a wallop.
ヒヒツ さ曹力ヾは
新開発されたバ卜ルス一ツだ!
例の組織力ヽら命がけで
盗んできた甲斐があったというもの
It was definitely worth
risking our lives to steal them.
Wait, that was the wrong building.
あ このマンシヨ ン違つた
My bad, Boss.
曹いやせん ボス
ゼ二一丿しの家は もつと先でした
Zeniru's house is a little further up.
失敗は誰にでもある !
Everyone makes mistakes!
肝心なのは反省し
活力ヽ曹ことだ 違う力ヽ!?
The important thing is
to learn from them. Am I right?
Yes, you're right!
団員 違いません
All right, then onward to Zeniru's!
丿\ンマ一へッ ド
では いざゼ二一丿しのもとへ
団員たちオ一 !
Thanks, bicycle guy!
少年あり力ヾとう
自転車のお兄ちゃん
サイ夕マ はうおおあ!
ハナクソついた指で
あっち向いてホイ 仕掛けて<るな!
Don't come asking to play rock, paper,
scissors with a booger on your finger!
夢力ヽ
A dream?
⑭キヤス夕一
F市で暴動を続けるテ口リス卜は
The terrorist group responsible for
the riots call themselves the Paradisers.
⑭桃源団と名乗つており
They have destroyed
a high-rise building in City F.
⑭ F市の高層 ビ丿しを破壊萱るなど
⑭手に負えない状態に
なつている模様で曹一
The situation seems to be
spiraling out of control.
We have just learned
the identity of their leader.
輸たつた今 犯人グル一プの
主犯の身元が判明しました ! 一
B-CLASS CRIMINAL – HAMMERHEAD
⑭巳級賞金首の
ハンマーへツドー
Hammerhead is a B-class criminal who has been
involved in several violent incidents in the past.
輸これまでにも数々の暴力
事件を起こし亡いま曹ー
He is a man of large stature,
⑭身長2mー5cm
体重2ー。kgの巨体を持ち一
standing 2.15 meters tall
and weighing 210 kilograms.
According to one report, he once fought twenty men
in a street brawl and sent them all to the hospital.
⑭路上のケン力で2。人を相手に_
⑭全員 病院送りにした経歴が
あるとの情報が入つ亡いま曹一
⑭桃源団力ヽらテレビ局に送られてきた
メツセ一ジによると一
The Paradisers sent the following
message to this TV station.
⑭働力ヽない者にも無償で衣食住が
提供される世の中になるまで一
"We will continue to riot until food, clothing, and shelter
are provided free of charge to those who do not work,"
⑭暴れ続けるなどと…
Sounds pretty boring.
amongst other unintelligible demands.
サイ夕マ つまんね一事件だな
⑭キヤス夕一ハンマ一へツ ドに
同調したメンバ一は…
Like Hammerhead, the group is made up of
unemployed young men with no motivation to work.
No need for me to get involved.
サイ夕マ
<今回は俺が行くまでもね一な>
Also, the group members all have shaven heads,
⑭キヤスタ一構成員の頭は
スキンへッ ドで統一され一
making them quite intimidating.
⑭非常に危険な雰囲気に
包まれていま曹一
⑭え一 外出された際に
スキンへッ ドを見力ヽけたら一
Those who encounter any shaven-headed men
on the street are advised to leave the area immediately.
⑭萱ぐに その場を離れてださい
・・ 何だと?
What?
サイ夕マ
俺と 力ヽぶつ亡んじゃね一力ヽ! >一
But that's—
They stole
my look!
I spend all this time trying to be a hero,
せつ力`ヒ一口一やつ亡亡も一
こんな真似されたら
俺も悪者扱いされるじゃね一力ヽ>
but if they keep acting up
I'll be treated like a villain!
I'm gonna smash them!
ぶつ演萱‥
男性ー 逃げろ一 !
Run!
It's them!
男性 2
ハゲが押し寄せ亡るぞお お
The Paradisers are coming!
こいつら
本気でぶつ飛んでやがる ! _
They aren't backing down!
This is too dangerous!
危険萱ぎる !
Stop right there, you pack of thugs!
無免ライダ一待亡 悪党ども ! 一
正義の自転車乗り
無免ライダ一参上!
むめん
The cyclist for justice, Mumen Rider, is here!
Mumen Rider has come to save us!
無免ライダ一が来てれたわ!
There's nothing to fear if he's here!
彼が来たなら もう安心だ
ヒ一口一力` だらん
A hero? What a joke!
Here I go!
無免ライダ一 行ぞ!
女性 キヤアア !
Somebody call an ambulance!
男性 誰力`救急車を呼ベ !
執事 ゼ二一ル様 ! お逃げださい
Mr. Zeniru, you must flee!
ゼ二一丿し う・ うむ し力`し
But running away from terrorists
would hurt my reputation.
テ口リス卜を相手に
逃げ出萱というのも
ワシのイメ一ジダウンだな
There's no need to leave.
ソ二ツク その必要はない一
あんたは運がいい
You're a lucky man,
俺との契約期間中に
こんなことが起きるとはな
having this occur while
I'm still under contract.
お お前はボデイ一ガ一 ドの !
But you're a bodyguard—
Oh, Sonic!
ソ二ツク君 ! 一
おお!
Can I leave this to you?
君に任せ亡も平気なのかね蝿一
The men coming are—
相手は…
ソ二ツク無論のこと
Of course.
案ずるなら連中の命だ
It's their lives you should worry about.
But please do think of a way
to dispose of the pile of corpses.
あんたらは死体の山を
どう処理萱る力ヽだけを
者え亡いればいい一
ツク桃源団…一
ソ二
The Paradisers...
A bunch of upstarts equipped
with some new type of battle suit.
聞いたことのない 新型の
バ卜丿しス一ツを装備した暴徒力ヽ>一
That and the B-class criminal Hammerhead.
巳級賞金首のハンマ一へツ ド一
He might have some backbone.
少しは骨がありそうだな
THE MODERN NINJA
Boss, you can see Zeniru's building
on the other side of the woods.
ボス この林を抜けた先に
見えるのが ゼ二一丿し邸…
People call it the Golden Turd.
通称 金のウンコ ビ丿しで萱ぜ
All right, let's go!
よし 行ぞ
There's something there.
イ可力ヽLヽる・‥
ソ二ツク
待つ亡たぞ ハンマ一へツ ド_
I've been waiting for you, Hammerhead.
Zeniru sent me.
ゼ二一ルの使いだ一
初めに言つ亡お一
Let me start out by saying...
俺は今まで戦った相手を
生力ヽし亡帰したことはない一
no opponent of mine has ever escaped alive.
今後もそのつもりだ一
I plan on keeping it that way.
When it comes to my work, I'm a perfectionist.
仕事は完璧にこな萱一
But if you surrender right now, I'll let you live.
今曹ぐ投降曹れば
死なずに済むが…
お前らはどう萱る?
So, what will it be?
グ工!
う うお一!
What is this?
ハンマ一へツ ド 何だ ? 一
What's going on?
何が起き亡いる蝿
Why is every—
何でみんな…
丿\ンマ一へッ ド
やつ ! やつベえええ! >
Shit!
そつたれ一‥
Bastard!
What's this now?
ソニック何をし亡いる
威嚇のつもり力ヽ?一
Trying to intimidate me?
You can't see me, can you?
俺が見えないんだろう ?
There you are!
ハンマ一へツ ド そこ力`あ つ !
うわ一 テ口リス卜だああ!
It's a terrorist!
No, I'm not!
ちげ
俺は違一つて !
So he decided to fight instead of run.
ソ二ツク
なんと逃げずに攻めてる力`一
おつと い力ヽんな
また悪いクセ力ヾ>
Oops, there goes my bad habit again.
ハンマ一へツ ド ははははは一
You're just a little dog
bought with Zeniru's money.
金で雇われたゼ二一ルの犬め
崇高な思想の下で戦う この俺が
You think someone like me,
who fights for a noble cause,
犬に負けるとでも思つた力`!
can lose to a dog?!
Yes, I see what he's up to.
ソ二ツク
なるほど 分力`りや萱い一
I see. He really is just a complete fool.
やはり馬鹿だな この男一
Couldn't he have at least tried to arrange
the rocks in a less obvious way?
もつと自然に誘い込むように
岩を配置できないの力ヽ?>
There are plenty more rocks
where those came from!
岩は まだまだ たさんある!
If you don't stop me, they'll keep coming.
俺を止めないと
どんどん飛んでくるぞぉ!
So you think you'll be able to deal with my speed
if you know which direction I'm coming from?
ソ二ツク
来る方向が分力`つ亡いれば一
俺のスビ一ドに対応できるとでも
思つ亡いるんだな
哀れな奴だ 乗つてやろう
How pathetic. But I'll play along.
In fact, I'll take you…
ソ二ツク
正面力`ら 真つ直ぐに一
straight on!
狩る !
He's too fast. I can't see him.
丿\ンマ一へッ ド
速Lヽ! やはり見えん ! >一
But it doesn't matter if I can't.
だが見えなてもいい ! 一
Because of this!
なぜなら !
Gotcha!
ハンマ一へツ ド もらつた!
Think about how stupid you were to face off
against me on your way down to Hell!
この俺に刃向力ヽったこと
あの世で悔いろ 惠力ヽ者め力ヾ!
終わつた‥・
It's over.
いや 残念だが手加減できな力`つ た
Unfortunately, I couldn't go easy on them.
Yes, Hammerhead's body is here too.
ああ
ハンマ一へツ ドの死体もここだ
I'll head back now—
で
は今力`ら戻~
The body disappeared?
ソ二ツク 死体が消えた ?
丿\ンマ一へッ ド
あ~ 危な力ヽつた ! >一
That was close!
Good thing he hit my head.
奴が刺したのが
頭でよ力ヽつた ! >一
My skull has always been
several times thicker than normal.
ずがいこつ
俺の頭蓋骨が通常の何倍も
分厚くてよ力ヽつた ! >一
Dammit. I don't know who that bastard was,
but one day I'm gonna kill—
クソオ! あの野郎一
<名前は知らんが
いつ力ヽ ぶつ殺し亡… ん?>一
Huh?
Now what?
また何かいるな
ん?一
Hm?
Oh, there you are.
As with the mosquito monster,
I once again underestimated my opponent's power.
ジ工 ノ ス 蚊の怪人に続き一
またし亡も俺は 相手の力を
見誤つてしまつたので曹一
油断した俺は
力ブ卜虫の返り討ちに遭い…
I let my guard down,
and Kabuto took advantage of that.
もしも あの場に
サイ夕マ先生がいなヵヽったら〟・
If Master Saitama had not been there,
I would certainly have been destroyed.
俺は確実に破壊されていました
I see.
クセ一ノ
そう力ヽ し力ヽし無事でよ力ヽったよ
Well, I'm glad you're okay—
Doctor…
博士
Master Saitama saved my life twice.
俺は またサイタマ先生に
命を救われたので曹
クセ一ノ博士に
一度救われた この命
You, Doctor Kuseno, restored my life to me.
そしてサイ夕マ先生に
助けられた俺の命は一
Later Master Saitama saved that same life,
and now he's saved it again.
またしても先生の手によつて…
ああ 大体分力`つたよ ジ工 ノ ス一
Yes, I get the picture, Genos.
とに力` そのサイタマ君が一
What you're trying to tell me is
how amazing this Saitama fellow is, right?
い力`に 萱ごい力`を
言いたいんだな オヌシは
Yes.
Genos, they're not ready just yet,
ジ工ノス
今回は間に合わな力ヽったが
今 新しいパ一ツを
開発し亡いるんだ一
but I am developing
a new series of augmentations.
When I replace your existing
parts with these new ones,
換装萱れば そのサイ夕マ君を
超えることができるかもしれない一
you may be able to surpass this Saitama.
I imagine he must possess an enormous amount
of strength for you to go on about him so.
オヌシに そこまで言わせるとは
彼は相当な実力者なんだろう
Yes.
What's your deal?
何だ お前 桃源団に入 り たいの力` ?
You here to sign up with the Paradisers?
サイ夕マ いや 違う
No, no.
I'm just a guy who's a hero for fun.
俺は趣味で
ヒ一口一をやつてる者だが
一身上の都合により
お前らを ぶつ演曹わ
For personal reasons,
I'm here to smash your heads in.
So, where are your followers?
で 手下たちはどこに?
Then, die!
ハンマ一へツ ド じやあ死ね!
ふう.
早この場を離れなければ…
I better get out of here quick.
丿\ンマ一へッ ド
あれ? 今 殴つたよな?>
Huh?!
I thought I punched him?
What a letdown.
力ヾつ
力
`りア
どな
These battle suits got me all excited.
バ卜丿しス一ツつ亡のに
少しワクワクし亡たのに一
手抜きなデザインな上に
機能は怪力だけかよ
But the design is lame,
and all they do is give you
superhuman strength.
丿\ンマ一へッ ド
このス一ツの入手に一
You have no idea how hard it was
to get hold of these things!
どれだけ苦労したこと力`…一
How could you know their value?!
壽様のようなアホには
」の価値が分かるまい‥
I've been looking for someone
to test the full power of this suit on!
俺もフ丿しパワ一をぶつける
実験台が欲し力ヽったところだ!
ツ! しやあツ ‥
Spin attack!
グルグル ア夕一ツク‥
サイタマ<この技 俺もガキの頃に
よ<やつ亡た…>
I used to use that move
all the time when I was a kid...
Huh?
えつ んな… バ力な…
No way...
Hammerhead, huh?
サイ夕マハンマ一へツ ド力ヽ‥・
こいつは俺に似ている>
He's a lot like me.
What the hell are you?!
貴様! 何者!
ぶぼつ ! !
ひいい~一
まままま 待亡!
W-Wait. I just wanted to get out of working...
俺は ただ
働きたくな力ヽつただけで…
サイ夕マ もう悪さ やめろよ
Don't be bad anymore, okay?
え? 俺を抹殺しに来たんじや…
Huh? So you're not going to kill me?
行け
ハンマ一へツ ド は はい ! _
Get outta here.
Okay!
ヒ工~
はあ… 帰る力ヽ…
Guess I'll go home.
ソニックハンマ一へツ ドは
どこに行った?
Where did Hammerhead go?
There's no one left but you.
ソ二ツク まだ残党がいたとはな
ん ハンマ一へツ ドなら
あっちに行つたけど 全裸で
Hammerhead went that way. Buck naked.
What's this?
何だ こりや…
おい 違うぞ
Hey, you got it wrong.
何が違うんだ
I got what wrong?
俺は桃源団の仲間 じ や ね一よ
I'm not one of the Paradisers.
You're lying.
嘘をつな
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
ふざけんなよ よ見ろよ !
Don't be dumb! Look at me!
I don't need to.
よ<見るも何も
その頭では言い逃れできないな
With that bald head, there's no denying it.
サイ夕マいや ほら! 俺だよ 俺!
No.
Look! It's me. Me!
趣味でヒ一口一やつ亡亡
割と活躍し亡る…
You know, the guy who's a hero for fun—
Never heard of you.
ソ二ツクお前など知らん
あ そう萱力`…
Oh, I see...
Either way, it doesn't matter.
ソ二ツク
それに どつちでもいいことだ
You read my attacks. Twice.
That's the real problem.
お前は俺の技を 2 度も見切つ た
それが問題だ一
俺は忍者の里に生まれ一
Born in a ninja village,
I've been perfecting
my techniques since childhood.
幼少の頃力ヽら
技の研鑽を重ねてきた…一
けんさん
その技をお前は見切つた一
Yet you saw right through them.
This I cannot allow.
許されないことをしたな…
サイ夕マ
<何言つ亡んだ コイツ…>
What's he talking about?
My pride won't have it.
俺のプライ ドが許さない
I don't care who you are.
I can't just let you walk away.
お前が誰だろうと
もう逃力ヾ曹ことはできない
嘘つけ
Oh, come on.
お前は ただ自分の技を
試したいだけだろ?一
You just want to try out your moves on me.
その無邪気な笑顔 見りゃ
分力ヽるぜ
I can tell by that innocent smile of yours.
速を超える
このスビ一ド>一
What do you think of this supersonic speed?
Of these shock waves?
そし亡衝撃波一
見える力`? 一
Can you even see me?
この速さについ亡これる力`?
How can you possibly keep up with me?
Um...
帰つ亡いい力`?
Can I go home?
Bastard!
ソ二ツク こいつ! !
Wind Blade Kick!
サイ夕マチ工ツクメイ卜一
Checkmate.
あつ! 萱まん!
Sorry!
That wasn't on purpose.
いや わざとじやないんだよ一
I meant to stop before hitting you,
but your momentum carried my fist into your...
寸止めしようと思ったら
勢いで ぶっヵヽっただけで〟・
We are experiencing technical difficulties. Please stand by.
俺は暗殺力ヽら用心棒まで
何でも請負う最強の忍者
I've worked every job
from assassin to bodyguard.
No ninja is more deadly.
I am Speed-o'-Sound Sonic!
だが仕事は しばらくおあずけだ一
But I'm putting my work on hold.
お前という好敵手を
見つけた力ヽらには一
Now that I've found
such a formidable opponent,
決着がつまで鍛錬あるのみ一
I'm dedicating myself
to training until we settle this.
名前を聞いておこう
Let me know your name.
サイタマだ
It's Saitama.
Saitama!
サイタマ!
次に会つた時が お前の最期だ!
Next time we meet, it'll be your demise!
Okay.
I, Speed-o'-Sound Sonic, the ultimate ninja,
究極の忍術で確実に仕留める !
速 ヽ 一
のノ一ツク力ヾな!
will bring you down without fail!
頑張れよ !
Train hard!
速のソ二ック? 誰で曹力ヽ?
Speed-o'-Sound Sonic?
Who is that?
その頭痛が痛いみたいな
名前の人物は?
And who would possess
such a redundant name?
サイ夕マ分力`らん一
Dunno.
いきなり現れて
ライ バ丿し宣言し亡去っていった
He suddenly appeared,
declared we were rivals, and took off.
先生がお困 り な ら俺が消 し ま萱が
If he is a nuisance, I will get rid of him.
Well, you're hardly different.
サイタマ お前も厄介だな一
...亡ゆ一力ヽ
何でまた来てんだよ一
Actually, why are you here again?
帰れよ 他人なんだ力`ら
Go home. It's not like we're related.
Master, I must become stronger—
ジ工ノス
先生 俺は強くならなければ…
サイ夕マ うるせええ一
Shut up!
俺は重大な問題に気づいこ
ショツクを受け亡る最中だ
I'm now aware of a serious problem
and am reeling from shock.
今日は帰つ亡れ 頼む力`ら
So I beg you, go home for today.
A serious problem?
重大な問題 ?
先生ほどの人が抱える
重大な問題とは何で曹力ヽ?
What could cause a problem
for someone as great as you?
教え亡ださい
Please share with me.
サイタマ 知名度が低い
No one knows who I am.
俺が趣味でヒ一口一を始め亡力ヽら
もう3年経つ一
It's been three years
since I first became a hero.
I've defeated many monsters
and evil organizations during that time.
今まで た<さん怪人だの
悪の軍団だのを退治してきた…一
I've never heard of any other
heroes doing as much as me.
他のヒ一ロ一が俺くらい
活躍をしてる現場なんて一
見たことがない ! _
もはや誰もが
知ってていいんじゃない力ヽ?一
Everyone in the world
should know me by now!
Isn't it weird that I don't
have any fans or anything?!
もつとファンと力ヽい亡も
不自然じゃないだろ一
今日 何亡言われたと思う ? _
You know what he said to me today?
「お前など知らん」だつてよ一
"Never heard of you."
Plus, everyone in town took me for a terrorist.
田〕の奴も俺を完全に
テ口リス卜扱いしやがつたしよ一
前に怪人力ヾ出た時は
俺力ヾ やつつけたつつ一のに・.・
They've all forgotten how
I beat those monsters for them!
ジ工ノス
確力ヽに先の二ユ一スでも>一
He is right.
The news report did not mention
Master Saitama or Speed-o'-Sound Sonic.
桃源団を撃退したのは一
速のソ二ックでもなく>一
無免ライダ一というヒ一口一の
お力ヽげであると報道していたな>
Instead, the credit for defeating the Paradisers
went to a hero called Mumen Rider.
まさ力ヽ… 先生!
サイ夕マあ?
Wait...
Master!
ジ工ノスヒ一口一名簿に
登録し亡ないんで曹力ヽ?
Are you listed with the Hero Registry?
HERO ASSOCIATION OFFICIAL HOMEPAGE
サイ夕マ
全国にあるヒー口ー協会の
施設でテス卜を受けー
"Take a test at any local branch
of the Hero Association.
If you score better than the cut-off,
you will be registered in the Hero Registry and
_定の水準を超えれば
ヒー口ー名簿に登録されー
正式にヒー口ーと
名乗ることを許されま萱ー
will be allowed to officially
call yourself a 'hero.'
Once you are recognized by the Association,
you are deemed a professional
協会に認められた者は
プ口とし亡ー
協会に寄付された募金がー
and will get paid from donations
collected by the Association.
働きに応じ亡
支払われま曹ー
All heroes in the public eye
are registered, professional heroes.
世間一般でいう
ヒー口ーとは_
名簿に登録された_
プ口ヒー口ーの
ことでありー
い<ら個人で
活動し亡い亡もー
You may be doing plenty of hero work,
but self-proclaimed heroes are really just weir… does…"
自称ヒーローでは
妄言を吐<変態ヨ
ジェノス変態とし力ヽ認識さねず
白い目で見られちゃうよ盧
"…weirdoes spouting nonsense
viewed with suspicion."
サイ夕マ つ
知らな力`つた…
I had no idea.
ジ工 ノ スは登録し亡んの力` ?
Genos, are you registered?
いえ 俺はいいで萱
No. I feel no need to.
登録しようぜ
Let's register! Register with me
and I'll make you my disciple.
一緒に登録してくれたら
弟子にしてやる力ヽら
行きましよう!
Let's go.
ハンマ一へツ ド
ひつ ひいいいいい~
ゆ... ゆる‥. 許し‥.
P-Please… F-Forgive me...
Pleading for his life after stealing
battle suits from the organization?
サイボ一グー組織力ヽらス一ツを
盗んでおいて一
命乞いとは一
どこまでも惠かな奴だ
He truly understood nothing.
Of course, we did let the theft take place
in order to collect data from the suits in the field.
サイボ一グ2ス一ツの実践デ一夕を
記録曹るために一
わざわざ泳がせていたんだがな
サイボ一グー 死体は?
And the body?
サイボ一グ2放つ とけ
Leave it.
丿\ンマ一へッ ド
<丈夫な頭蓋骨に生んでくれて>一
Thanks for giving me my thick skull, Mommy.
ありがとう 母ちやん一
俺 働よ
I promise I'll get a job!
APPLICATION FOR
HERO TEST
⑭アナウンサ一
今日は若者の労働問題に詳しい一
Our guest today is Mr. Majimeda, an expert on
the labor issues confronting young people today.
⑭専門家のマジメダ氏を
ゲス卜にお招きいたしました
⑭マジメダよろしお願いしま萱
Thank you for having me.
⑭さ亡昨今 桃源団のように
As we saw with the Paradiser incident recently,
⑭働く意欲のない若者の増加が
深刻化していま曹が
there's an increase in young people
who lack all motivation to work.
⑭この現状を どう思われま萱力` ?
Can you comment on this phenomenon?
Even in the case of the Paradisers,
I think they've been influenced by irresponsible lyrics
俺も大して
変わらな力ヽつたつ亡こと力ヽ…
I'm not so different...
in popular songs like "Don't Give Up on Your Dreams"
and "Make Your Dreams Come True."
⑭ マジメダ 夢を諦めるな 一
⑭ 夢は叶えるものだ と力ヽ…
サイ夕マ無職のあいつと…
from those unemployed guys.
People who believe such hogwash end up
making excuses for themselves and become discouraged.
⑭マジメダ無責任に
投げられた言葉に一
⑭感化されてはいかんので萱よ一
⑭そういう奴は
結局しょうもない言い訳して一
挫折曹るんで曹よ
敷力ヽれた線路を進まない…
サイ夕マ
一歩間違えれば俺も>一
One wrong step and I could've been one of them.
あいつみたいに
なつ亡たの力ヽな…>
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
Lまあ・‥
さあ 行きましよう 先生
Ready to go, Master?
Y-Yeah.
HERO
TEST
SITE
Next
Time
The
Ultimate
Mentor
丿\ンマ一へッ ド
え一 この度 改心いたしました一
Err… I'm the recently reformed Hammerhead.
ハンマ一へツ ドで萱一
え一 来週の予告を
させていただくにあたり一
Before I introduce next week's episode,
I'd like to do a little PR for myself.
まず自己P 円力`ら
したいと思いま萱一
あ そういうの 菫りません力`? _
Oh? You won't allow that?
次回 ワンパンマン
第5話 『究極の師』 一
Next time on episode five
of One-Punch Man,
"The Ultimate Mentor."
そつ力ヽ 俺にも
こんな先生力ヾいたら一
Yeah, if I'd had a mentor like him,
maybe my life would've been different.
人生 達つ亡たのかもしんねえな…